http://www.emtcompany.com/pages/privacy-policy

Cart
"Close Cart"
Information Gathering and Use
EMTCompany possesses solitary ownership of all gathered information on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent any information gained, except as outlined in this policy. Information collected from our customers is used to serve you with relevant information, such as order status updates and order confirmations. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, telephone numbers, and e-mail addresses.
Order
Once you proceed to check-out, all your information is protected by Paypal. Any information gained by EMTC will not be shared or sold to any third parties, except those outlined in the Sharing section of this policy.
Cookies
Here we customize certain Web page content depending on your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. Any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie will not be shared with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This permits us to personalize your shopping experience and give you a sense of constant familiarity, which makes each visit simple and convenient.
Log Files
We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information to gain profit nor do we distribute or share any of this information with any third parties.
Sharing
In some instances, we may utilize third party companies to perform functions on behalf of EMTC. Some of these functions may include: marketing assistance, customer service, data analysis, order fulfillment, and package delivery. As our business continues to grow, we may obtain or sell business units or subsidiaries. In these type of transactions, customer information is one asset that would be transferred. In this capacity, your information transferred would still be used in a way consistent to the pre-existing Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information when it is required by law. This applies when we feel that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Minor
We do not sell or intend to do business with anyone under the age of 18 years old. If you are under the age of 18, you must have a consenting parent or guardian with you at the time of purchase. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. EMTC is committed to the protection of welfare and privacy of children.
Notification of Changes
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time at our own discretion. Please be aware of any changes by visiting this page.
Last Update
The Privacy Policy contained within this document became officially effective June 22, 2010.
Address
EMTCompany.com 2114 S. Susan St. Santa Ana, Ca. 92704
Added to cart!
